(Sheldon:)Here you go.
- Great. Come on in.
- What, you don't say thank you?
(Howard:)It's my suitcase.
I lent it to you two years ago.
(Raj:)I should tell you
I broke the wheel and the handle.
(Raj:)So is everyone from Bernadette's company
going to Vegas?
(Howard:)No, just me, her,
and a couple of the bigwigs.
(Howard:)It's part of a bonus she got.
(Raj:)Cool. Did she discover a cure
for something?
(Howard:)Not exactly. They spent a ton of money
developing this dandruff medication...
(Howard:)...that had the side effect
of horrible anal leakage.
(Raj:)Is there a good anal leakage?
(Howard:)Anyway, it was Bernie's idea to rebrand
the stuff as a cure for constipation.
(Raj:)Way to make lemonade, you know, from
around the corner where fudge is made.
- Hey, I got a favor to ask.
- Sure.